{
  "id": "Web Development Acronyms",
  "name": "Web Development Acronyms",
  "editable": false,
  "data": [
    {
      "front": "CSS",
      "back": "Cascading Style Sheets"
    },
    {
      "front": "DHTML",
      "back": "Dynamic HyperText Markup Language"
    },
    {
      "front": "HTML",
      "back": "HyperText Markup Language"
    },
    {
      "front": "WML",
      "back": "Wireless Markup Language"
    },
    {
      "front": "XHTML",
      "back": "Extensible HyperText Markup Language"
    },
    {
      "front": "XML",
      "back": "Extensible Markup Language"
    },
    {
      "front": "ASP",
      "back": "Active Server Pages"
    },
    {
      "front": "CGI",
      "back": "Common Gateway Interface"
    },
    {
      "front": "JSP",
      "back": "JavaServer Pages"
    },
    {
      "front": "PHP",
      "back": "PHP Hypertext Preprocessor/Personal Home Page"
    },
    {
      "front": "RoR",
      "back": "Ruby on Rails"
    },
    {
      "front": "SSI",
      "back": "Server Side Includes"
    },
    {
      "front": "ASP",
      "back": "Application Service Provider"
    },
    {
      "front": "AWS",
      "back": "Amazon Web Services"
    },
    {
      "front": "RSS",
      "back": "Really Simple Syndication"
    },
    {
      "front": "S3",
      "back": "Amazon Simple Storage Service"
    },
    {
      "front": "YUI",
      "back": "Yahoo! User Interface"
    },
    {
      "front": "CRUD",
      "back": "Create, Read, Update and Delete"
    },
    {
      "front": "DBMS",
      "back": "Database Management System"
    },
    {
      "front": "SQL",
      "back": "Structured Query Language"
    },
    {
      "front": "CRON",
      "back": "Command Run ON"
    },
    {
      "front": "IIS",
      "back": "Internet Information Services"
    },
    {
      "front": "VPS",
      "back": "Virtual Private Server"
    },
    {
      "front": "FTP",
      "back": "File Transfer Protocol"
    },
    {
      "front": "HTTP",
      "back": "HyperText Transfer Protocol"
    },
    {
      "front": "HTTPS",
      "back": "Secure HypterText Transfer Protocol"
    },
    {
      "front": "SSH",
      "back": "Secure Shell"
    },
    {
      "front": "SSL",
      "back": "Secure Sockets Layer"
    },
    {
      "front": "WAP",
      "back": "Wireless Application Protocol"
    },
    {
      "front": "W3C",
      "back": "World Wide Web Consortium"
    },
    {
      "front": "WAI",
      "back": "Web Accessibility Initiative"
    },
    {
      "front": "WCAG",
      "back": "Web Content Accessibility Guidelines"
    },
    {
      "front": "AJAX",
      "back": "Asynchronous JavaScript And XML"
    },
    {
      "front": "DOM",
      "back": "Document Object Model"
    },
    {
      "front": "JS",
      "back": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
      "front": "CRAP",
      "back": "Contrast, Repetition, Alignment, Proximity"
    },
    {
      "front": "CVS",
      "back": "Concurrent Versions System"
    },
    {
      "front": "GUI",
      "back": "Graphical User Interface"
    },
    {
      "front": "SVN",
      "back": "Subversion"
    },
    {
      "front": "WYSIWYG",
      "back": "What You See Is What You Get"
    },
    {
      "front": "CMYK",
      "back": "Cyan Magenta Yellow Key"
    },
    {
      "front": "FLA",
      "back": "Flash Authoring File"
    },
    {
      "front": "GIF",
      "back": "Graphics Interchange Format"
    },
    {
      "front": "JPEG",
      "back": "Joint Photographic Experts Group"
    },
    {
      "front": "PNG",
      "back": "Portable Network Graphics"
    },
    {
      "front": "PSD",
      "back": "PhotoShop Document"
    },
    {
      "front": "RGB",
      "back": "Red Green Blue"
    },
    {
      "front": "SVG",
      "back": "Scalable Vector Graphics"
    },
    {
      "front": "SWF",
      "back": "Small Web Format/ShockWave Flash"
    },
    {
      "front": "AVS",
      "back": "Address Verification System"
    },
    {
      "front": "CSC/CVV",
      "back": "Card Security Code/Card Verification Value"
    },
    {
      "front": "MID",
      "back": "Merchant ID"
    },
    {
      "front": "FAQ",
      "back": "Frequently Asked Questions"
    },
    {
      "front": "CPC",
      "back": "Cost Per Click"
    },
    {
      "front": "CPM",
      "back": "Cost Per 1000 Impressions"
    },
    {
      "front": "CTR",
      "back": "Click Through Rate/Ratio"
    },
    {
      "front": "PPC",
      "back": "Pay Per Click"
    },
    {
      "front": "PR",
      "back": "PageRank"
    },
    {
      "front": "SEO",
      "back": "Search Engine Optimization"
    },
    {
      "front": "SERP",
      "back": "Search Engine Results Page"
    },
    {
      "front": "XSS",
      "back": "Cross-Site Scripting"
    },
    {
      "front": "CSRF",
      "back": "Cross-Site Request Forgery"
    },
    {
      "front": "CNAME",
      "back": "Canonical Name"
    },
    {
      "front": "DNS",
      "back": "Domain Name System"
    },
    {
      "front": "DTD",
      "back": "Document Type Definition"
    },
    {
      "front": "ICANN",
      "back": "Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers"
    },
    {
      "front": "IP",
      "back": "Internet Protocol"
    },
    {
      "front": "TLD",
      "back": "Top-Level Domain"
    },
    {
      "front": "URL",
      "back": "Uniform Resource Locator"
    },
    {
      "front": "WWW",
      "back": "World Wide Web"
    }
  ]
}
